<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Strings regarding the Attractions -->
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>
    
    <string name="parthenon">Parthenon</string>
    <string name="parthenon_info">The Parthenon is the main ancient structure on the Acropolis,
        a hill in the center of Athens. It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site, the symbol 
        of Athens and the most famous of the surviving structures from the world of ancient Greece.</string>
    <string name="parthenon_address">Acropolis, Athens</string>
    
    <string name="acropolis">The Acropolis</string>
    <string name="acropolis_info">Athens\' top must-see attraction and a UNESCO site is the Acropolis,
        High City or Sacred Rock, a hill overlooking the city and home to the most recognizable
        symbol of the city, the Parthenon.</string>
    <string name="acropolis_address">Athens 105 58</string>
    
    <string name="temple_zeus">Temple of the Olympian Zeus</string>
    <string name="temple_zeus_info">The remains of this massive temple stand southeast of the Acropolis.
        Built in the 2nd century during the Roman era, the temple of Zeus Olympios
        was the largest in ancient Greece.</string>
    <string name="temple_zeus_address">Vassilisis Olgas Ave., Athens</string>
    
    <string name="theater_dionysos">Theater of Dionysos</string>
    <string name="theater_dionysos_info">On the southern slope of the Acropolis the pedestrian street
        of Dionysiou Areopagitou is the site of two ancient performance venues – the Dionysos 
        Theatre and the Odeion Theatre of Herodes Atticas.</string>
    <string name="theater_dionysos_address">Dionysiou Areopagitou St., Athens, southern slope of Acropolis</string>
    
    <string name="hadrian_arch">Hadrian\'s Arch</string>
    <string name="hadrian_arch_info">This triumphal arch was erected in the 2nd century AD in honor
        of the Roman emperor Hadrian. It was probably constructed before Hadrian's visit to Athens on 131/132AD.</string>
    <string name="hadrian_arch_address">Amallias Ave, Athens (entrance to the site of Temple of Olympian Zeus,
        south of National Gardens)</string>

    
    <string name="roman_agora">Roman Agora</string>
    <string name="roman_agora_info">Visitors to the Agora in Athens get to stroll between what remains
        of the Roman Forum or center of the city from 19 to 11BC.</string>
    <string name="roman_agora_address">North of Acropolis, east of Ancient Agora. Main entrance from side street
        off Adrianou St. east of Stoa of Attalos.</string>

    <string name="ancient_agora">Ancient Agora</string>
    <string name="ancient_agora_info">The Agora or "gathering place" was the heart of ancient Athens.
        People would come here to do business, shop, be entertained, hear philosophers expounding their views,
        attend court, go to school, socialize and conduct politics.</string>
    <string name="ancient_agora_address">24 Adrianou St., Athens 105 55</string>

    <string name="plaka">Plaka</string>
    <string name="plaka_info">The Plaka, a neighborhood at the foot of the Acropolis, will be one of the most
        enchanting places you visit in Athens even though it is geared towards tourists it has retained
        a charm and picturesque quality.</string>
    <string name="plaka_address">Neighborhood northeastern side of Acropolis between Syntagma Square and
        Monastiraki Square</string>

    <!-- Strings regarding the Museums -->
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>

    <string name="acropolis_museum">The Acropolis Museum</string>
    <string name="acropolis_museum_info">The Acropolis Museum is ultra modern, bright and state-of-the art.
        There are five main sections to guide you through a unique perpective on the monumental hill.</string>
    <string name="acropolis_museum_address">Entrance from Dionisiou Areopagitou 15, Makriyianni, Athens 117 42</string>
    <string name="acropolis_museum_phone">+30 210 900 0901</string>

    <string name="historical_museum">National Historical Museum Athens</string>
    <string name="historical_museum_info">The building which houses this museum has a long and eventful 
        history.Among the artifacts on display are traditional costumes, memorabilia, flags, furniture, 
        medals and personal items which belonged to historical figures. There is an art collection of historical 
        paintings created by both Greek and foreign artists.</string>
    <string name="historical_museum_address">Old Parliament Building, Kolokotronis Square, 13 Stadiou St., Athens</string>
    <string name="historical_museum_phone">+30 210 323 7617</string>

    <string name="benaki_museum">Benaki Museum</string>
    <string name="benaki_museum_info">The Islamic Collection is one of several branches of the Benaki Museum;
        it is housed in the Kerameikos building complex. The museum in the center of Athens comprises
        two neo-classical buildings which are both listed. The buildings have many ornamental features.</string>
    <string name="benaki_museum_address">1 Koumpari St. &amp; Vas. Sofias Ave, Athens 106 74</string>
    <string name="benaki_museum_phone">+30 210 367 1000</string>

    <string name="goulandris_museum">Goulandris Museum of Cycladic Art</string>
    <string name="goulandris_museum_info">The Cyclades are a group of Greek isles in the Aegean Sea.
        The Cycladic culture flourished on the islands from 3200BC to 2000BC and the archaeological findings
        on display in this museum give us insight into the islands' ancient civilization.</string>
    <string name="goulandris_museum_address">Main Building - Neofitou Douka 4, Athens 106 74</string>
    <string name="goulandris_museum_phone">+30 210 722 8321</string>

    <string name="herakleion_museum">Herakleidon Museum</string>
    <string name="herakleion_museum_info">This private museum is in the shadow of the Acropolis in a neo-classic
        building dating back to 1898. The museum\'s goal is to introduce visitors to the world of fine arts by
        highlighting the work of specific artists who have made a major contribution to art.</string>
    <string name="herakleion_museum_address">Herakleidon 6, Thissio, 118 51 Athens</string>
    <string name="herakleion_museum_phone">+30 210 346 1981</string>

    <string name="archeological_museum">National Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="archeological_museum_info">o see the largest collection of archaeological findings from
        Greece visit this centrally located museum. The huge neo-classical building was expanded in several
        stages to make room for the growing collection.</string>
    <string name="archeological_museum_address">44 Patission St. Athens, 106 82</string>
    <string name="archeological_museum_phone">+30 213 214 4800</string>

    <string name="athens_museum">Athens City Museum</string>
    <string name="athens_museum_info">With so many of the city\'s sites devoted to the ancient
        civilizations of Athens it is refreshing to visit this museum which focuses on the modern
        history of the Greek capital.</string>
    <string name="athens_museum_address">5-7 Paparrigopoulou St. Athens 105 61</string>
    <string name="athens_museum_phone">+30 210 324 6164</string>

    <string name="folk_museum">Greek Folk Art Museum</string>
    <string name="folk_museum_info">The Museum of Greek Handicraft was founded in 1918 and in 1959 its
        name was changed to the Museum of Greek Folk Art. The museum has four sections each housed in a
        different location.</string>
    <string name="folk_museum_address">Central Building - Kidathineon 17, Plaka</string>
    <string name="folk_museum_phone">+30 210 324 5957</string>

    <!-- Strings regarding the Activities -->
    <string name="category_acivities">Activities</string>

    <string name="delphi_trip">Delphi Day Trip from Athens</string>
    <string name="delphi_trip_info">Immerse yourself in the myths and monuments of classical Greece
        on this full-day tour of Delphi from Athens.Explore the UNESCO-listed archeological site of
        Delphi with an expert guide and learn how the city was considered the ‘Center of the World’
        in ancient Greece.</string>
    
    <string name="islands_cruise">Hydra, Poros and Egina Day Cruise from Athens</string>
    <string name="islands_cruise_info">Discover three beautiful Greek islands on this full-day cruise from
        Athens. Sail to Poros, Hydra and Egina in the Saronic Gulf and enjoy free time at each island to
        stroll, sightsee and shop as you wish.</string>
    
    <string name="sounion_trip">Cape Sounion and Temple of Poseidon Half-Day Trip from Athens</string>
    <string name="sounion_trip_info">Marvel over one of Greece’s most photographed monuments on this half-day
        tour to the Temple of Poseidon from Athens. You’ll have chance to get up close to the ancient monument,
        explore ruins dating back to 44 B.C and soak up the impressive coastal views.</string>

    <string name="riviera_trip">City Sightseeing Athens, Piraeus &amp; Beach Riviera Hop-On Hop-Off Tour</string>
    <string name="riviera_trip_info">Experience the best of Athens in one day and your own way, with this City Sightseeing
        hop-on hop-off Athens bus tour. . Travel around by open-top double-decker bus and create your own sightseeing
        itinerary.</string>

    <string name="sky_dinner">Dinner in the Sky Athens</string>
    <string name="sky_dinner_info">Eat dinner in a revolving restaurant suspended in the sky during this 1.5-hour
        experience in Athens. From a bird\'s eye view at 165 feet (50 meters) in the air, get views of the city of
        Athens lit up at night</string>

    <string name="bar_tour">Athens Bar Hopping Tour</string>
    <string name="bar_tour_info">Experience the electric atmosphere of Athens by night on this 3-hour bar-hopping
        tour. Join your local guide and fellow party-lovers for an evening of Greek-style entertainment and get the
        inside scoop on the city’s nightlife.</string>

    <string name="corinth_trip">Corinth Half-Day Trip from Athens</string>
    <string name="corinth_trip_info">Explore the ruins of ancient Corinth and see the Corinth Canal on this Athens
        half-day tour.  Stroll around the relics of Corinth, once an influential ancient Greek and Roman city, and then
        visit the seaside town of Kehreai before your return to Athens.</string>
    
    <string name="walking_tour">Hidden Athens Walking Tour and Picnic: Plaka and the Hills of Athens</string>
    <string name="walking_tour_info">Escape the well-trodden tourist track and discover a quieter side of Athens on
        this leisurely 3.5-hour to 4-hour walking tour. With a local guide, explore the tucked-away areas around the
        slopes of the Acropolis and uncover their ancient and recent past.</string>

    <!-- Strings regarding the Night Life -->
    <string name="category_night_life">Night Life</string>
    
    <string name="wine_bar">Wine O\'Clock</string>
    <string name="wine_bar_info">A cozy winebar on walking distance from Acropolis Museum.Its owners, Andreas and Alex
        welcome you very friendly, and will give you their best advice about their delicious wine and appetizers.</string>
    <string name="wine_bar_address"> Lempesi 10, Athens 117 42</string>
    <string name="wine_bar_phone">+30 694 837 8922</string>
    
    <string name="brettos_bar">Brettos Bar</string>
    <string name="brettos_bar_info">A little gem of a distillery in the Plaka area. Beautiful deco, delectable self
        distilled spirits and friendly service make for a delightful cocktail. A must see on a trip to Athens!</string>
    <string name="brettos_bar_address">Kydathinaion 41 Plaka, Athens</string>
    <string name="brettos_bar_phone">+30 210 323 2110</string>

    <string name="taf_art">Taf The Art Foundation</string>
    <string name="taf_art_info">A really cool bar with an open courtyard where you can relax with a well-made cocktail.
        A bit hidden away, but that only adds to the experience. There is also an art gallery on the premises, but make
        sure you come early if you want to see the art</string>
    <string name="taf_art_address">Normanou 5 Monastiraki, Athens 105 55</string>
    <string name="taf_art_phone">+30 210 323 8757</string>

    <string name="a_bar">A for Athens Cocktail Bar</string>
    <string name="a_bar_info">The outside rooftop bar is busy as it has great view. Recommended for a cool drink
        with excellent view of the Acropolis and the surrounding areas so be sure not to forget your camera!</string>
    <string name="a_bar_address">Miaouli 2 - 4 Monastiraki, Athens 105 54</string>
    <string name="a_bar_phone">+30 210 324 4244</string>

    <string name="clumsies">The Clumsies</string>
    <string name="clumsies_info">There\'s a reason this place is one of the best. he cocktail list is
        expansive and original. The bartenders are artists with flavor. The atmosphere is excellent.It\'s
        worth paying extra for the care and attention.</string>
    <string name="clumsies_address">Praxitelous 30, Athens 105 61</string>
    <string name="clumsies_phone">+30 210 323 2682</string>

    <string name="local_pub">The Local Pub</string>
    <string name="local_pub_info">A traditional pub with amazing beers. The selection of beers is excellent,
        the staff is superb, and the atmosphere of regular guests made it an excellent place.</string>
    <string name="local_pub_address">Chaimanta 25, Athens 152 34</string>
    <string name="local_pub_phone">+30 694 086 4443</string>

    <string name="thesis">Thesis 7</string>
    <string name="thesis_info">Great little oasis on a hot day in Athens. High on positive vibes, great atmosphere,
        friendly family owners, and friendly patrons. A must visit for anyone looking for a fun evening.</string>
    <string name="thesis_address"> Agiou Filippou 7 Monastiraki, Athens 105 55</string>
    <string name="thesis_phone">+30 216 900 0790</string>

    <string name="prima_cava">Materia Prima Cava &amp; Wine Bar</string>
    <string name="prima_cava_info">An excellent place to taste carefully selected wines,local and international!
        The space is beautifully decorated,wine oriented and you can also have delicious dishes to
        combine with your wine.</string>
    <string name="prima_cava_address">Falirou 68 Koukaki, Athens 117 41</string>
    <string name="prima_cava_phone">+30 210 924 5935</string>

</resources>